<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Clever Eggplant</string>

    <string name="menu_title">The Clever Eggplant</string>
    <string name="sanity_title">TTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="textBullshit">
        <item>
            Upcoming session: 26 March, 2015 @ StartX\n
            Emphasis: flaming cocktails!\n
            I\'m planting the menu, please be patient!\n
            Previous week\'s menu:\n\n
            (PREVIOUS) March 12, 2015\n
            Alien Brain Hemorrhage\n
            Peach schnapps, Bailey\'s, blue curacao, grenadine\n\n
            Pho-shop Cocktail\n
            Gin, simple syrup, lime juice, cucumber, basil\n\n
            Fantastic Lake\n
            Sake, Cointreau, brandy, lemon, blue curacao, tonic water\n\n
            Ginger Basil Grapefruit Spritzer\n
            Grapefruit, simple syrup, ginger, basil, club soda\n\n
            Mint Juleps\n
            Bourbon, simple syrup, mint\n\n
            Laughter in the Rain\n
            Vodka, peach schnapps, lemon juice, simple syrup\n\n
            Bee String\n
            Tequila, lemon juice, honey, jalepeno
        </item>
        <item>The Clever Eggplant is an informal bar at StartX, which is Stanford\'s startup incubator. The bar is hosted by StartX-affiliate Weeby.co and staffed by a bartender, David, and Weeby\'s office manager, Rachel. By pulling a pair of tall tables and a few stools over next to a sink, the bar appears every two weeks to create a fun, relaxed, and playful atmosphere for its patrons. Regardless of if they want to relax with a sparkling fruity drink, or savor a stiff spirit-forward cocktail, or simply refresh themselves with a non-alcoholic libation before a long drive home, we can accommodate the diverse interests of our patrons.\n\n
           In May 2014, David, a newly employed software developer, got pulled into one of Weeby\'s weekly game nights at StartX. There, he met Rachel, who pointed out the large quantities of hard liquor that they had on hand. David had been wanting to learn to mix drinks, and so they struck a mutually beneficial arrangement. Together, they started an informal bar every other game night, serving cocktails free of charge. Rachel procured the ingredients for the bar and printed out each night\'s menu. David selected each night\'s drinks and served them to generous and enthusiastic patrons. On the night of August 14, 2014, the unrefined but scrappy bar opened for the first time.\n\n
           The first few sessions at the bar were challenging. Unseasoned, David would forget all sorts of equipment each week: his measurement jigger, or his mixing tins, or (most disastrously) his citrus juicer. His inexperience meant that even when fully equipped, he would often be hard pressed to serve the deluge of eager patrons who would swarm the bar. But session after session, the drinks came out a little faster, developed more sophistication, and the bar was able to create an enjoyable atmosphere.\n\n
            <br></br>
           Though it still has a long way to go, The Clever Eggplant has significantly matured since its opening night. It now offers everything from solid classic cocktails to idiosyncratic original drinks to fantastical layered shooters like the Alien Brain Hemorrhage. If you\'ve been a patron of the bar, then we\'d like to thank you for showing up and making the bar the success that it is. If you\'ve never come by, then please drop by the next time we\'re open, take a seat, check out our menu, order a cocktail, and stay a moment at our wonderful bar.
        </item>
        <item>Audi</item>
        <item>Why are we The Clever Eggplant?\nThe bar was nameless for its first six months of operation. Our name reflects our origins as a supporting fixture of StartX\'s board game nights. One night, a few of us were playing Apples to Apples. David played the green card "Clever", prompting the other players to choose cards that they thought were evocative of cleverness. One of his friends had no good answers and played "Eggplant" in response to get rid of an otherwise useless card. The ludicrous combination of those cards amused David so much that he made it the name of the bar.\nDoes David work for StartX?\nNo, and neither does Rachel, for that matter. Rachel\'s company, Weeby, graduated from StartX\'s startup incubation program, which is how she is affiliated with them. Likewise, David has a friend whose company also graduated from StartX, which is how David was introduced to game nights. Neither David nor his company have any affiliation with StartX. He simply mixes there on their good graces.\nHow did David start bartending?\nHis mixing began when he received a mixology book for his birthday. He likes to say that reading the book and watching Youtube videos accounts for 10%% of his skill and knowledge, while the other 90%% comes from patrons at the bar bombarding him with drink requests until he could handle them all.</item>
        <item>Mortality</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="david_blurb">David is, by day, a software engineer at Refresh, Inc., a startup that aggregates data from a variety of professional and social networks and recommends conversation topics. He drinks sparingly while bartending, as he ironically has embarrassingly unimpressive alcohol tolerance. Besides mixing drinks for the bar, David also chooses the drinks, worked on the modern menu layout, and built and manages the website. He also powerlifts recreationally, practices Judo at Stanford, and enjoys reading books in the office before work and at coffee shops during the weekend.
    </string>
    <string name="rachel_blurb">Rachel is the office manager for Weeby.co, a software startup that builds a game engine and games for their platform. Besides keeping her colleagues alive at the office, she puts together Weeby\'s game nights at StartX\'s facility, even when The Clever Eggplant is not in session. Every week she pulls together game nights with dozens of attendees and arranges enough food to feed all of them. Bar weeks present further challenges: she prints the night\'s menu and stocks the bar with citrus and sodas and herbs and liquors and frequent one-off ingredients. Rachel may not be the face of the bar, but she is its invaluable backbone, and without her there would be no game nights at all. Outside of work, Rachel enjoys running outdoors and dancing at clubs.
    </string>
    <string name="stephanie_blurb">Stephanie is the visual designer for Jelli, Inc., a startup that produces a cloud-based ad platform for radio. When David wanted to build new logos and redesign the menu, he turned to his high school friend for her professional expertise. Stephanie put in many hours to build numerous revisions of The Clever Eggplant\'s logo, art assets, typography, and layout. Everything that makes the menu and website beautiful is a piece of her work.
    </string>
    <string name="jason_blurb">Jason is a prognostics intern at NASA, measuring the performance of their aviation equipment. Hailing from Trinidad, he explored the Bay Area and ended up meeting David in a coffee shop. The two of them agreed to overcome their lack of Android experience and are building a mobile app for The Clever Eggplant. Jason is an avid photographer and astronomer. He combined these to build a star identification algorithm in his free time. David has also never seen a human consume so much vodka so easily in one sitting.
    </string>
</resources>
